<resources>
    <string name="app_name">contact_shield_demo</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="title_FAQ">FAQ</string>
    <string name="title_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="notPositiveStatus">"I have <b>not</b> tested positive."</string>
    <string name="positiveStatus">"I tested positive for Covid-19."</string>
    <string name="FAQ1">"How are interactions calculated?"</string>
    <string name="answer1">"We use Bluetooth LE to sense how close you are to other users who also has the app downloaded. If we estimate that you have been within 6 feet of other users we record an interaction."</string>
    <string name="FAQ2">"What happens when I self-report a positive test?"</string>
    <string name="answer2">"With your permission, anonymous alerts will be sent to the people who have been near you and have potentially been exposed to the virus."</string>
    <string name="FAQ3">"When will I get alerted?"</string>
    <string name="answer3">"Whenever anyone anonymously self-reports a positive test, we alert people who we think may also be exposed to the virus."</string>
    <string name="FAQ4">"Where can I get tested?"</string>
    <string name="answer4">"Covid-19 tests can be done at the testing centers and health departments. To get tested, contact your state and local health department or your medical provider"</string>
    <string name="FAQ5">"Does this App really work without my personal information?"</string>
    <string name="answer5">"Anonymity is our top priority. No personal details are required when you download and use the App."</string>
    <string name="report_results"> <u> "Report your results >>" </u></string>
    <string name="report_positive_heading"> <b>"Share Your Positive Test Result"</b></string>
    <string name="report_positive_body">"If you have been tested positive for COVID-19, you can share your test results to help notify others who may have been in contact with you. This will let others know they should monitor for symptoms. Only those who have been exposed will receive a notification."</string>
    <string name="verify_heading"> <b>"Enter Your TAN Code"</b></string>
    <string name="verify_caption">"This unique verification code is provided by your testing center, and it is used to verify your positive test result."</string>
    <string name="test_date_heading"><b>"Test Date"</b></string>
    <string name="test_date_caption">"Your test date helps the app know when you may have been contagious and notify others who have been in contact with you from the past 14 days."</string>
    <string name="disable_app_caption">"When the App is disabled, your device will not send or receive signals from other users."</string>
    <string name="disable_PK_caption">"When Periodic Key upload is disabled, the device will stop uploading your periodic keys to the server, and others will not be able to download your periodic key if you are tested positive. New periodic keys will be generated and stored locally on the device."</string>
    <string name="disable_notification_caption">"When notifications are turned off, your device will not receive any notifications for potential exposures or interactions with other users."</string>
    <string name="alert_heading"><b>"You have been in contact with a Covid-19 Patient!"</b></string>
    <string name="alert_body">"Someone you have been in contact with recently have self-reported positive. Please self-quarantine or get tested at your local testing center."</string>
    <string name="verification_methods_heading">"Choose Verification Method"</string>
    <string name="verification_method1_heading">"Scan QR code"</string>
    <string name="verification_method1_description">"Register your test by scanning the QR code that can be found in your testing documents."</string>
    <string name="verification_method2_heading">"Request TAN code"</string>
    <string name="verification_method2_description">"Please call us if you have been diagnosed of COVID-19 but do not have a QR code."</string>
    <string name="teleTAN_heading">"How this works"</string>
    <string name="teleTAN_description">"Call the hotline to request a TAN:"</string>
    <string name="teleTAN_hotline">"+1(213)-425-8730"</string>


</resources>
